maypalo.com 2017-02-17

# Privacy Policy | Maypalo

The privacy of our visitors to Maypalo.com is important to us. At Maypalo.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Maypalo.com, and how we safeguard your information. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Personal Information**  
As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment on our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside Maypalo.com.

 **Cookies**  
We also use third party advertisements on Maypalo.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Maypalo.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

 **Amazon  Affiliate Program**

Maypalo.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com

For any further queries or questions you can contact us through our [Contact Us](http://maypalo.com/contact-us/) page.
